I've enjoyed so many meetings with Prime Minister. He's such
an incredible student. And every time I see him, he wants to
learn about technology, artificial intelligence, the
potential and opportunity for India, the impact on India
society and industry. And so I was delighted to be here to
talk about it. India, as you know, is also home of some of
the world's greatest computer scientists. So this is a great
opportunity. Artificial intelligence is also a new industry,
a new manufacturing industry that's very important. And so
I'm looking forward to partnering with India in a very deep
way to make that possible. We have many partnerships with
India. For one, we're helping India gain access to our most
advanced technologies. We're partnering with internet
companies like Yoda and end-to-end networks and to create
the latest generation AI supercomputers in India for all of
the startups. India is the home of the third largest startup
economy. And so this new generation of startups are all
based on AI. And in order to do so, you have to have AI
infrastructure. Just the number of partnerships we have all
over India. Every IIT has an NVIDIA AI center of excellence.
We're teaching professionals, we're teaching students how to
upskill into this new world of AI. AI in a lot of ways is
very complicated technology, but in the end, what it enables
a country to do is take advantage of technology, take
advantage of computers in a way that has never been possible
before. And so AI really democratized computing. This is
India's moment. You have to seize the opportunity.